Guide to the New-York Historical Society Collection of Geographic Images circa 1600-2006 PR 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: New York City Views - Manhattan, 50413
  - Subseries IA: MANHATTAN - BOXED MATERIAL, 50554
    - Manhattan - Boxed Material - Street Views, 50562
      - Fifth Avenue (50th to 52nd street), 174464 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Fifth Avenue (52nd to 54th street), 174465 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Fifth Avenue (55th to 60th street), 174466 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Fifth Avenue (60th to 72th street), 174467 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Fifth Avenue (72th to 89th street), 174468 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Fifth Avenue (90th - 143rd street), 174474 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Sixth Avenue (to 32nd street), 174475 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Sixth Avenue (32nd to 57th street), 174478 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Seventh Avenue (11th street to 42nd street), 174479 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Seventh Avenue (42nd street to 59th street), 174480 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Seventh Avenue (from 110th street on), 174481 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Eighth Avenue (Abingdon square to 31st street), 174482 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Eighth Avenue (31st to 57th street), 174483 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Eighth Avenue (110th street and up), 174486 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Ninth Avenue (12th to 49th street), 174487 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Tenth Avenue, 174488 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Eleventh Avenue, 174489 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Twelfth Avenue, 174490 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Thirteenth Avenue, 174491 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Avenue A (to 24th street), 174492 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Avenue B (lower east side), 174493 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Avenue C, 174494 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Avenue D, 174495 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Manhattan - Boxed Material - Neighborhoods, 51852
      - Chinatown, 174614 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Five Points (Later Paradise Park), 174615 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Greenwich Village (folder 1), 174626 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Greenwich Village (folder 2), 174627 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Harlem, 174630 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Inwood, 174631 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Lower East Side (folder 1), 174632 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Lower East Side (folder 2), 174633 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Manhattanville (folder 1), 174634 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Manhattanville (folder 2), 174635 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Stuyvesant Town (formerly Gashouse District), 174636 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Washington Heights, 174637 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Greenwich Village (Balducci's), 174638 (Box 44a, Folder 1)
      - Greenwich Village (Building Gutted by fire), 174639 (Box 44a, Folder 2)
      - Greenwich Village (Interiors), 174640 (Box 44a, Folder 3)
      - Greenwich Village (Morton Street Dock), 174641 (Box 44a, Folder 4)
      - Greenwich Village (Store Windows), 174642 (Box 44a, Folder 5)
      - Greenwich Village (Street Scenes), 174643 (Box 44a, Folder 6)
      - Greenwich Village (Washington Square Park), 174644 (Box 44a, Folder 7)
    - Manhattan - Boxed Material - Parks and Gardens, 51853
      - Battery Park (park views), 174645 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Battery Park (views toward water), 174646 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Battery Park (views toward water: aquarium), 174647 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Battery Park (views toward water: with Castle Garden and before use as Aquarium), 174648 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Battery Park (views toward park: general), 174649 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Battery Park (views toward park: with Castle Garden), 174650 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Bolton Garden (W. 158th street), 174651 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Bowling Green, 174652 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Bryant Park (formerly Reservoir Square), 174653 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Central Park- pre-1860s views (Fort Fish and McGowan's Pass), 177085 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Central Park- pre-1860s views (Park Preparation), 177087 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Central Park- pre-1860s views (Squatters' shacks), 177097 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Central Park-Maps, 177098 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Central Park-Birds-eye views, 177099 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Central Park-General Views, 177100 (Box 46, Folder 6-7)
      - Central Park-General Views with Animals, 177102 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Central Park-Winter views, 177103 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Central Park-Buildings-General Arsenal, 177104 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Arsenal including zoo, 177105 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Belvedere Castle, 177106 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Casino, 177109 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Mount St. Vincent, 177110 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Miscellaneous, 177111 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Central Park-Bridges-Bow Bridge, 177113 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Central Park-Bridges-Miscellaneous, 177114 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Central Park-Fountains-Bethesda Fountain and Terrace, 177115 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Central Park-Fountains -Bethesda Fountain and Terrace, 177116 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Central Park-Lake and Ponds -The Lake, 177146 (Box 48, Folder 2-4)
      - Central Park-Lake and Ponds- Pond near 59th st., 177149 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Central Park-Lake and Ponds -Reservoir, 177150 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Central Park-The Mall, 177151 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
      - Central Park-Playgrounds, 177153 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Central Park-Roads-Transverse Road #2 at 79th street, 177154 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Central Park-Roads-Transverse Road #4 at 97th street, 177155 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Central Park-Statuary-Simon Bolivar Statue, 177156 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Central Park-Statuary-Eagle Statue, 177157 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Central Park-Statuary-Alexander Hamilton Statue, 177158 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Central Park-Statuary-Obelisk, 177159 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Central Park-Statuary-Daniel Webster Statue, 177160 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Central Park-Statuary-Miscellaneous, 177161 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Central Park-Walks and Woods, 177162 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Central Park-Activities-Coaching, 177163 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Central Park-Activities-Ice Skating, 177164 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Central Park-Activities-May Parties, 177165 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Central Park-Activities-Tennis, 177166 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Block House, 177107 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Boat House, 177108 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Tavern on the Green, 177112 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - City Hall Park from South, 177167 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - City Hall Park from South - Bartlett and derivatives, 177168 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - City Hall Park from East, 177169 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - City Hall Park from West, 177170 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - City Hall Park from North, 177171 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - City Hall Park fountain, 177172 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Duane Park, 177173 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Elgin Botanic Garden, 177174 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Fort Tryon Park, 177175 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Fort Washington Park, 177176 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Gramercy Park, 177177 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Highbridge Park and Harlem River, 177178 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Inwood Park, 177179 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Isham Park, 177180 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Jones Wood, 177181 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Lion Park, 177182 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Madison Square, 177183 (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
      - Morningside Heights and Park, 177185 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Mount Morris Park, 177186 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Mulberry Bend Park, 177187 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Riverside Park, 177189 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Saint John's Park, 177191 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Seward Park, 177192 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Strauss Park, 177193 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Stuyvesant Square, 177194 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - Tompkins Square Park, 177195 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Union Square, 177196 (Box 51, Folder 15-16)
      - Washington Square Park, 177198 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Manhattan - Boxed Material - Buildings, 51854
      - Buildings-Armories and Arsenals-General, 51856 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Armories and Arsenals-Shot Tower, East 53rd Street, 51911 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Armories and Arsenals-7th Regiment Armory, various locations, 51912 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Armories and Arsenals-71st Regiment Armory, Park Ave. and 34th Street, 51913 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Bathhouses- SEE: Buildings-Government-Public Baths, 51857 (Box .)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues- Composite Images, 51916 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues- set of G. Stacey's Photographs of NYC Churches, 51917 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-A miscellaneous, 51918 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Advent Episcopal Church, 177210 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-All Angels Episcopal Church, 177230 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-All Saints Roman Catholic Church, 177231 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-All Souls Unitarian Church, 177232 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Amity Baptist Church, 177233 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Annunciation Episcopal Church, 177234 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Asbury Methodist Church, 177235 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Ascension Episcopal Church, 177236 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-B miscellaneous, 177237 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Beloved Disciple, Episcopal Church of the, 177238 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Beth-El, Temple, 177239 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Bethel, African Methodist Episcopal Church, 177240 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-B'nai Jeshurun, 177241 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Bloomingdale Baptist Church, 177242 (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Bloomingdale Reformed Dutch Church, 177243 (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Brick Presbyterian Church, 177244 (Box 52, Folder 23)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Broadway Tabernacle, 177245 (Box 52, Folder 24)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Broome Street Dutch Reformed Church, 177246 (Box 52, Folder 25)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-C miscellaneous, 177247 (Box 52, Folder 26)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Calvary Baptist Church, 177248 (Box 52, Folder 27)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Calvary Episcopal Church, 177249 (Box 52, Folder 28)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Carmine Street Presbyterian Church, 177250 (Box 52, Folder 29)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Cedar Street Prebyterian Church, 177251 (Box 52, Folder 30)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Cenacle of Saint Regis Roman Catholic Church, 177252 (Box 52, Folder 31)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Charles Street United Presbyterian Church, 177253 (Box 52, Folder 32)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Chelsea Methodist Episcopal Church, 177526 (Box 52, Folder 33)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Christ and St. Stephen's Church, 177557 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Christ Church, 177558 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Christ's Lutheran Church, 177559 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Christ the Savior Russian Orthodox Church, 177560 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Collegiate Baptist Church, 177561 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Convent of Mary Reparatrix Retreat House, 177562 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Convent of the Sacred Heart, 177563 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Corpus Christi Episcopal Church, 177564 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Czentochauer Chasam Sopher, 177565 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-D miscellaneous, 177566 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Disciples, Church of the, 177567 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Divine Paternity, Church of the, 177568 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Duane Street Methodist Episcopal Church, 177569 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Duane Street Presbyterian Church, 177570 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-E miscellaneous, 177571 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-East Baptist Church, 177572 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Emanu-el, Congregation, 177573 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Epiphany, Church of the, 177574 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-F miscellaneous, 177575 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Fifth Avenue Presbyterian Church, 177576 (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-First Baptist Church, 177577 (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-First Methodist Church, 177578 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-First Moravian Church, 177579 (Box 53, Folder 23)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-First Presbyterian Church, 177580 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-First Reformed Episcopal Church, 177581 (Box 53, Folder 25)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Floating Church of our Savior, 177582 (Box 53, Folder 26)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Fourteenth Street Presbyterian Church, 177583 (Box 53, Folder 27)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Fourth Avenue Presbyterian Church, 177584 (Box 53, Folder 28)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Free Church for Seamen and Boatmen, 177592 (Box 53, Folder 29)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Friends Meeting House, 177593 (Box 53, Folder 30)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-G miscellaneous, 177594 (Box 53, Folder 31)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-German Evangelical Presbyterian Church, 177595 (Box 53, Folder 32)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Good Shepherd, Church of the, 177596 (Box 53, Folder 33)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Grace Church (exterior), 177597 (Box 53, Folder 34)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Grace Church (interior), 177598 (Box 53, Folder 35)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Grace Gospel Church, 177599 (Box 53, Folder 36)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Greene Street Methodist Episcopal Church, 177600 (Box 53, Folder 37)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Greenwich Presbyterian Church, 177602 (Box 53, Folder 39)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Greenwich Dutch Reformed Church, 177601 (Box 53, Folder 38)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-H miscellaneous, 177671 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Harlem Reformed Dutch Church, 177672 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Heavenly Rest, Episcopal Church of the, 177673 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Holy Communion, Episcopal Church of the, 177674 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Holyrood Episcopal Church, 177675 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Holy Spirit, Episcopal Church of the, 177676 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Holy Trinity, Episcopal Church of the, 177677 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Holy Trinity, Harlem Episcopal Church of the, 177678 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Holy Trinity, Settlement Church of the, 177679 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-I miscellaneous, 177680 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Incarnation, Episcopal Church of the, 177681 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Incarnation Parish, Episcopal Chapel of, 177682 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Intercession, Church of the, 177683 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-J-K miscellaneous, 177684 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-John Street Methodist Church, 177685 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-L miscellaneous, 177686 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Laight-Street Baptist Church, 177687 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Little Church Around the Corner (Episcopal Church of the Transfiguration), 177688 (Box 54, Folder 18-19)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-M miscellaneous, 177690 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Madison Avenue Methodist Episcopal Church, 177691 (Box 54, Folder 21)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Madison Avenue Presbyterian Church, 177692 (Box 54, Folder 22)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Madison Square Presbyterian Church, 177693 (Box 54, Folder 23)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Marble Collegiate Church, 177694 (Box 54, Folder 24)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Mariners Baptist Chapel, 177695 (Box 54, Folder 25)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Mariners Methodist Episcopal Church, 177696 (Box 54, Folder 26)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Messiah, Unitarian Church, 177697 (Box 54, Folder 27)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Metropolitan Baptist Church, 177698 (Box 54, Folder 28)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Middle Dutch Chuch, 177699 (Box 54, Folder 29)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Mother Cabrini High School Roman Catholic Chapel, 177700 (Box 54, Folder 30)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Mount Washington Presbyterian Church, 177701 (Box 54, Folder 31)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-N miscellaneous, 177702 (Box 54, Folder 32)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Nativity, Church of the, 177703 (Box 54, Folder 33)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-North Baptist Church, 177704 (Box 54, Folder 34)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-North Reformed Dutch Church, 177705 (Box 54, Folder 35)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Northeast Reformed Dutch Church, 177706 (Box 54, Folder 36)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-O miscellaneous, 177707 (Box 54, Folder 37)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Our Lady of Guadalupe Roman Catholic Church, 177708 (Box 54, Folder 38)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Our Lady of Mount Carmel Roman Catholic Church, 177709 (Box 54, Folder 39)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-P miscellaneous, 177710 (Box 54, Folder 40)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Prospect Hill Reformed Church, 177711 (Box 54, Folder 41)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Puritans, Presbyterian Church of the, 177712 (Box 54, Folder 42)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Church of the Puritans, 177713 (Box 54, Folder 43)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-R miscellaneous, 178983 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Reformed Dutch Chuch, 178984 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Resurrection, Episcopal Chuch of the, 178985 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Riverside Baptist Church, 178986 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Rose Hill Methodist Episcopal Chuch, 178987 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-SAA-SAH miscellaneous, 178988 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. A-J miscellaneous, 178989 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Agnes Chapel of Trinity Parish, 178990 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Andrew's Church, 178991 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Ann's Roman Catholic Church, 178992 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Bartholomew's Church, 178993 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Clement's Episcopal Church, 178994 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Esprit, Eglise Francoise du, 178995 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. George's Episcopal Church, 178996 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. George's Roman Catholic Church, 178997 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. George's Greek Catholic Church, 178998 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. George and St. Demetrios, Church of, 178999 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Ignatius' Episcopal Church, 179000 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. James Episcopal Church, 179001 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. James Lutheran Church, 179002 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. James Roman Catholic Church, 179003 (Box 55, Folder 21)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. John's Episcopal Chapel, 179004 (Box 55, Folder 22-23)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. John's German Evangelical Church, 179006 (Box 55, Folder 24)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. John's Methodist Church, 179007 (Box 55, Folder 25)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. John the Divine, Episcopal Church of the, 179008 (Box 55, Folder 26-27)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. John the Evangelist, Episcopal Church of the, 179010 (Box 55, Folder 28)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Joseph's Roman Catholic Chuch, 179011 (Box 55, Folder 29)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. K-Z miscellaneous, 179012 (Box 55, Folder 30)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Luke's Episcopal Church, 179026 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Luke's Lutheran Church, 179027 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Mark's Evangelical Lutheran Church, 179028 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Mark's Episcopal Church in the Bouwerie, 179029 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Mary's Roman Catholic Church, 179030 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Michael the Archangel, Chapel of, 179031 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Michael's Episcopal Church, 179032 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Nicholas, Collegiate Church of, 179033 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Nicholas, Greek Autocephalous Church of, 179034 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Patrick's Roman Catholic Cathedral, 179035 (Box 56, Folder 10-11)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Old St. Patrick's Roman Catholic Cathedral, 179037 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Paul's Episcopal Church and churchyard, 179038 (Box 56, Folder 13-16)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Peter's Episcopal Church, 179042 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Phillips' Episcopal Church, 179043 (Box 56, Folder 18)